<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="episode_titles">
        <item>Mercy</item>
        <item>The Damned</item>
        <item>Monsters</item>
        <item>Some Guy</item>
        <item>The Big Scary U</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="episode_nums">
        <item>Episode #1</item>
        <item>Episode #2</item>
        <item>Episode #3</item>
        <item>Episode #4</item>
        <item>Episode #5</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="episode_dates">
        <item>October 22, 2017</item>
        <item>October 29, 2017</item>
        <item>November 5, 2017</item>
        <item>November 12, 2017-</item>
        <item>November 19, 2017</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="episode_overviews">
        <item>Rick, Maggie, and Ezekiel rally their communities together to take down Negan.
        Gregory attempts to have the Hilltop residents side with Negan, but they all firmly stand behind Maggie.
        The group attacks the Sanctuary, taking down its fences and flooding the compound with walkers.
        With the Sanctuary defaced, everyone leaves except Gabriel, who reluctantly stays to save Gregory,
        but is left behind when Gregory abandons him. Surrounded by walkers,
        Gabriel hides in a trailer, where he is trapped inside with Negan.</item>
        <item>Rick\'s forces split into separate parties to attack several of the Saviors\' outposts,
            during which many members of the group are killed;
            Eric is critically injured and rushed away by Aaron.
            Jesus stops Tara and Morgan from executing a group of surrendered Saviors.
            While clearing an outpost with Daryl, Rick is confronted and held at gunpoint by Morales,
            a survivor he met in the initial Atlanta camp, who is now with the Saviors.</item>
        <item>Daryl finds Morales threatening Rick and kills him;
            the duo then pursue a group of Saviors who are transporting weapons to another outpost.
            Gregory returns to Hilltop, and after a heated argument,
            Maggie ultimately allows him back in the community.
            Eric dies from his injuries, leaving Aaron distraught.
            Despite Tara and Morgan\'s objections, Jesus leads the group of surrendered Saviors to Hilltop.
            Ezekiel\'s group attacks another Savior compound, during which several
            Kingdommers are shot while protecting Ezekiel.</item>
        <item>Ezekiel\'s group is overwhelmed by the Saviors,
            who kill all of them except for Ezekiel himself and Jerry. Carol clears the inside of the compound,
            killing all but two Saviors, who almost escape but are eventually caught by Rick and Daryl.
            En route to the Kingdom, Ezekiel, Jerry, and Carol are surrounded by walkers,
            but Shiva sacrifices herself to save them. The trio returns to the Kingdom,
            where Ezekiel\'s confidence in himself as a leader has diminished.</item>
        <item>After confessing their sins to each other,
            Gabriel and Negan manage to escape from the trailer.
            Simon and the other lieutenants grow suspicious of each other,
            knowing that Rick\’s forces must have inside information.
            The workers in the Sanctuary become increasingly frustrated with their living conditions,
            and a riot nearly ensues,
            until Negan returns and restores order.
            Gabriel is locked in a cell, where Eugene discovers him sick and suffering. Meanwhile,
            Rick and Daryl argue over how to take out the Saviors, leading Daryl to abandon Rick.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="episode_title">Mercy</string>
    <string name="episode_num">Episode 1</string>
    <string name="episode_title_show">The Walking Dead</string>
    <string name="episode_num_season">Season 8</string>
    <string name="episode_date">October 22, 2017</string>
    <string name="episode_channel">AMC</string>

    <string name="episode_overview">
        Rick, Maggie, and Ezekiel rally their communities together to take down Negan.
        Gregory attempts to have the Hilltop residents side with Negan, but they all firmly stand behind Maggie.
        The group attacks the Sanctuary, taking down its fences and flooding the compound with walkers.
        With the Sanctuary defaced, everyone leaves except Gabriel, who reluctantly stays to save Gregory,
        but is left behind when Gregory abandons him. Surrounded by walkers,
        Gabriel hides in a trailer, where he is trapped inside with Negan.

    </string>
    <!--<string name="movie_poster">@drawable/movie_poster</string>-->

    <!--TABS-->
    <string name="episode_tab1">Overview</string>
    <string name="episode_tab2">Comments</string>
</resources>