<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="person_names">
        <item>Chadwick Aaron Boseman</item>
        <item>Andrew Lincoln</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="person_birthdays">
        <item>November 29, 1977 (age 40)</item>
        <item>September 14, 1973</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="person_from">
        <item>Anderson, South Carolina, U.S.</item>
        <item>London, England, UK </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="person_biographies">
        <item>Boseman was born and raised in Anderson, South Carolina,
            the son of Carolyn and Leroy Boseman, both African Americans.
            His mother was a nurse and his father worked at a textile factory,
            keeping an upholstery business as well. Boseman graduated from T. L. Hanna High School in 1995.
            In his junior year, he wrote his first play, Crossroads, and staged it at the school
            after a classmate was shot and killed. He studied at Howard University in Washington, DC,
            graduating in 2000 with a bachelor of fine arts in directing. One of his teachers was Phylicia Rashad,
            who became a mentor. She helped raise funds so that Boseman and some classmates could attend
            the Oxford Mid-Summer Program of the British American Drama Academy in London,
            to which they\'d been accepted.She helped raise funds so that Boseman and some classmates could attend
            the Oxford Mid-Summer Program of the British American Drama Academy in London,
            to which they\'d been accepted.She helped raise funds so that Boseman and some classmates could attend
            the Oxford Mid-Summer Program of the British American Drama Academy in London,
            to which they\'d been accepted.</item>
        <item>Andrew Lincoln is a British actor. Lincoln spent his early childhood in Hull, Yorkshire
            before his family relocated to Bath, Somerset when he was age 10.
            He was educated at Beechen Cliff School in Bath,
            and then the prestigious Royal Academy of Dramatic Art in London.
            His father is a civil engineer and his mother is a nurse Lincoln's first big</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="person_profils">
        <item>@drawable/chadwick_profil</item>
        <item>@drawable/andrew_profil</item>
    </array>

    <array name="person_images">
        <item>@drawable/movie_image</item>
        <item>@drawable/show_image</item>
    </array>

    <string name="person_tab1">Infos</string>
    <string name="person_tab2">Movies</string>
    <string name="person_tab3">TV Shows</string>
    <string name="person_tab4">Comments</string>

    <string name="person_biography">Biographie:</string>
</resources>