<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="season_num">Season 8</string>
    <string name="season_title_show">The Walking Dead</string>

    <string-array name="seasons_nums">
        <item>Season 1</item>
        <item>Season 2</item>
        <item>Season 3</item>
        <item>Season 4</item>
        <item>Season 5</item>
        <item>Season 6</item>
        <item>Season 7</item>
        <item>Season 8</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="seasons_eps">
        <item>6</item>
        <item>13</item>
        <item>16</item>
        <item>16</item>
        <item>16</item>
        <item>16</item>
        <item>16</item>
        <item>16</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="seasons_date_begin">
        <item>October 31, 2010</item>
        <item>October 16, 2011</item>
        <item>October 14, 2012</item>
        <item>October 13, 2013</item>
        <item>October 12, 2014</item>
        <item>October 11, 2015</item>
        <item>October 23, 2016</item>
        <item>October 22, 2017</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="seasons_date_end">
        <item>December 5, 2010</item>
        <item>March 18, 2012</item>
        <item>March 31, 2013</item>
        <item>March 30, 2014</item>
        <item>March 29, 2015</item>
        <item>April 3, 2016</item>
        <item>April 2, 2017</item>
        <item>April 15, 2018</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="seasons_overviews">
       <item>
        Sheriff\'s deputy Rick Grimes wakes from a coma discovering a world overrun by zombies.
           After befriending Morgan Jones, Rick travels alone to Atlanta to find his wife Lori, his son, Carl,
           and his police partner, Shane Walsh, encountering other survivors.
           The group travels to the Centers for Disease Control (CDC),
           but find from the sole remaining CDC member that no cure exists for the epidemic.
       </item>
        <item>
        Traveling from Atlanta, Rick\'s group takes shelter at Hershel Greene\'s farm while they search
            for Carol\'s missing daughter, Sophia.
            Tensions between Rick\'s group and Hershel\'s family worsen after it is discovered
            that Hershel has kept friends and family turned into zombies, including Sophia,
            in his barn. Shane and Rick\'s friendship becomes increasingly unhinged
            when Lori reveals that she is pregnant, and Rick is forced to kill Shane in self-defense.
            Carl then shoots Shane in the head after he reanimates.
            The noise draws zombies, forcing Rick\'s group and Hershel\'s surviving family to evacuate the farm.
        </item>
        <item>
        Eight months after fleeing Hershel\'s farm,
            Rick\'s group finds a prison, which they clear of zombies to make their new home.
            Lori dies in childbirth, and Rick becomes withdrawn.
            Meanwhile, Andrea is rescued by Michonne and the two discover Woodbury,
            a fortified town led by a man known as the Governor.
            He learns of Rick\'s group at the prison, leading to conflict between them.
            Rick\'s group eventually raids and destroys Woodbury,
            but the Governor has Andrea ultimately killed and escapes.
            Woodbury\'s citizens live with Rick\’s group at the prison.
        </item>
        <item>
        Several months after the Governor\'s attack,
            a deadly flu kills many of the population at the prison.
            The Governor finds his former right-hand men and kills them,
            taking over their group and destroys the prison.
            Rick\'s group are forced to separate and flee, but not before Hershel and the Governor are killed.
            The survivors divide, face their own trials and meet new faces before
            finding signs pointing to a safe haven called Terminus.
            One by one, they reunite at Terminus, but all the group are captured for some unknown purpose.
        </item>
        <item>
        Rick discovers the residents of Terminus engage in cannibalism,
            but the group manage to destroy Terminus and reunite.
            Some are injured and kidnapped to Grady, a hospital run by corrupt cops and doctors.
            When the remaining survivors regroup, they are approached by Aaron,
            inviting them to join a fortified community called Alexandria.
            They are initially welcomed, but Rick\'s group realize the residents
            have not faced the zombie threat directly. Morgan, who has been searching for Rick,
            arrives and is shocked to see Rick killing an Alexandrian, who has been abusing his wife, in anger.
        </item>
        <item>
        The residents of Alexandria put more trust in Rick\'s group to protect the town better.
            A group known as the Wolves use a zombie horde to attack Alexandria,
            and many lives are lost before the living regain control.
            While recovering, they learn of a community called the Hilltop,
            who offer to help trade supplies if they can end the threat of the extortionist
            Saviors led by a man named Negan. Although Rick\'s group decimate one Savior outpost,
            they are later caught by Negan, and forced to swear loyalty to him.
        </item>
        <item>
        Negan murders Glenn and Abraham to coerce Rick\'s loyalty.
            Rick initially submits, but Michonne persuades him to fight back,
            and recruits a community called the Scavengers for help.
            Meanwhile, Rosita and Eugene make a bullet to kill Negan.
            When this fails, Negan forcibly recruits Eugene as a Savior.
            Separately, Carol and Morgan befriend Ezekiel of the Kingdom, another community,
            while Maggie and Rosita rally the Hilltop. Negan,
            the Saviors and the turncoat Scavengers attack Alexandria,
            but it is repelled by Sasha\'s sacrifice and the aid of Kingdom and Hilltop soldiers.
        </item>
        <item>
        Rick, Maggie, and Ezekiel rally their communities into war against Negan and the Saviors.
             Losses are heavy on both sides: many of the Kingdom soldiers are killed,
            Alexandria falls to a Savior attack, and Carl is bitten by a walker;
            before euthanizing himself, Carl convinces Rick to seek a peaceful end to the war
            and restart society anew. Negan is forced to weed out disloyalty in his ranks,
            and asserts the only way to end the war is to wipe out all of Rick\'s allies.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="season_episodes">16</string>
    <string name="season_date_begin">October 22, 2017</string>
    <string name="season_date_end">April 15, 2018</string>

    <string name="season_overview">
        Rick, Maggie, and Ezekiel rally their communities to flood the Sanctuary with walkers, trapping Negan.
        During the war, key Savior members grow suspicious of each other while the Hilltop and
        Kingdom are overwhelmed by the Saviors. Alexandria is attacked after Negan is freed.
        \nAs Carl retreats the residents to the sewers,
        they are horrified to discover Carl has been bitten.

    </string>
    <!--<string name="movie_poster">@drawable/movie_poster</string>-->

    <!--TABS-->
    <string name="season_tab1">Overview</string>
    <string name="season_tab2">Crew</string>
    <string name="season_tab3">Episodes</string>
    <string name="season_tab4">Comments</string>
</resources>